Christina Thai

Proactive and meticulous management professional offering 8+ years of extensive customer service experience. Proven to consistently meet productivity, business and customer service objectives. Skillfully work with all employees to enhance performance and improve day-to-day processes. Diplomatic in resolving internal and customer issues to maximize satisfaction.

EMPLOYMENT

September 2020 – Present

ACCOUNTING ADMINISTRATOR - Dien Realty

- + Handle accounts payable and accounts receivable for all business accounts.
- + Create detailed journal entries, track and balance all income statements and expenses.
- + Reconcile monthly business accounts.
- + Formulate monthly balance statements and income statements.
- + Issue monthly payroll and formulate yearly T4s.
- + Record and process monthly tax remittance and quarterly GST filings.
- + Prepare monthly statements, facilitate incoming payments and outgoing checks.
- + Daily data entry and financial reporting into accounting software (LoneWolf Technologies).
- + Facilitate sign-up process with realtors and transfer of licenses between brokerages.
- + Corresponded with real estate agents, vendors and clients via e-mail.
- + Assist real estate agents, manager and staff with other accounting duties as needed.

May 2020 – September 2020

CONVEYANCER – AWM Alliance

- + Administration duties including assisting the public with inquiries.
- + Corresponded with real estate agents, clients and strata agents via e-mail.
- + Prepared and processed Form B's using Citrix and the AWM database.
- + Organized and prepared documentation for residential and commercial conveyancing.

July 2019 – March 2020

OFFICE MANAGER - Cactus Club Cafe

- + Prepared payroll data for 100+ employees while upholding confidentiality expectations.
- + Organized and tracked Accounts Payable of store based invoices via Excel and RosNet.
- + Processed and accurately balanced all cash received, including tip outs.
- + Met deadlines with data entry of weekly numbers to be submitted to Head Office.
- + Updated and input all current/new employee HR information via Squirrel and Ultipro.
- + General office duties such as daily cash routines, maintaining filing systems, organizing office operations and contributing to team effort.

July 2017 – July 2019

RECEPTION, CONVEYANCE ASSISTANT – Sutton Centre Realty

- + Kept reception area clean and neat to give visitors positive first impression.
- Answered telephone calls to field inquiries from clients, vendors and various other callers seeking information.
- + Performed various administrative functions, including filing paperwork, sorting/delivering mail and office cleaning and organization.
- + Data entry to provide clerical support to agents during the sales process.
- + Operate scanners, facsimile machines and photocopiers.
- + Process contracts for sale/purchase of real estate.
- Handled filing systems for both short and traditional real estate transactions.

March 2015 – July 2017

MANAGER, BARTENDER, SERVER - Bao Down Gastropub + Raw Bar/ OG

- Hired, trained and mentored staff to maximize effectiveness.
- + Completed bi-weekly payroll and tip-outs for 30 employees via Squirrel and Excel Spreadsheets.
- + Created bi-weekly Front House schedule.
- + Purchased and managed monthly inventories of raw materials and components on work floor.
- + Applied strong leadership talents and problem-solving skills to maintain team efficiency and organize workflows to meet any daily demand.
- + Set, enforced and optimized internal policies to maintain efficiency and responsiveness to demands.

June 2013 – Mar 2015

MANAGER, SERVER, BARTENDER - Firepots Restaurant

- Created efficient work schedules for each team member to maintain deadlines and keep shifts properly staffed.
- + Completed bi-weekly payroll and tip-outs for 30
- Hired, trained and mentored staff to maximize effectiveness.
- + Purchased and managed monthly inventories of raw materials and components on work floor.

Aug 2012 – June 2013

GARDE MANGER/ DESSERT LINE COOK - Cardero's Restaurant

- + Received food orders and cooked items quickly to complete entire order together and served hot.
- + Prepared identical dishes numerous times daily with consistent care, attention to detail and quality.
- Cleaned counters, food preparation areas and equipment with sanitizing spray to prevent crosscontamination from raw meat and other items.
- + Maintained well-stocked stations with supplies and spices for maximum productivity.
- + Upheld optimal staff and customer protections by monitoring food handling, storage, use of kitchen equipment, sanitation and safety protocols.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021

BACHELOR OF ARTS – Simon Fraser University

- + Minor in Sociology
- + Minor in Gender Studies

Jan 2022 – November 2022

Jan 2016 – June 2016

Sept 2012 – June 2013

Sept 2011 – June 2012

UX DESIGN DIPLOMA – Career Foundry

NAIL TECHNICIAN CERTIFICATION - London School

HAIR DESIGN CERTIFICATION – Vancouver Community College

ACE-IT COOKS TRAINING – Burnaby Central Secondary